[{
	"Question": "What year was Kangaroo Point Park officially opened?",
	"answerA": "1794",
	"answerB": "1988",
	"answerC": "2000",
	"answerD": "2010",
	"correctAnswer": "D"
},
{	"Question": "How many levels does the amphitheatre have?",
	"answerA": "6",
	"answerB": "8",
	"answerC": "10",
	"answerD": "12",
	"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{	"Question": "What first opened on this site in 1867?",
	"answerA": "Church",
	"answerB": "School",
	"answerC": "Hospital",
	"answerD": "Police Station",
	"correctAnswer": "B"
},
{	"Question": "How many versions of the sun are in this artwork?",
	"answerA": "5",
	"answerB": "6",
	"answerC": "7",
	"answerD": "8",
	"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{	"Question": "What is the highest object on top of St Mary's?",
	"answerA": "Cross",
	"answerB": "Bell",
	"answerC": "Gargoyle",
	"answerD": "Antenna",
	"correctAnswer": "A"
},
{	"Question": "This wreath represents Australia and which other country?",
	"answerA": "England",
	"answerB": "Scotland",
	"answerC": "USA",
	"answerD": "New Zealand",
	"correctAnswer": "D"
},
{	"Question": "Which big bridge can you see from this foot bridge?",
	"answerA": "Gateway Bridge",
	"answerB": "Goodwill Bridge",
	"answerC": "Go Between Bridge",
	"answerD": "Storey Bridge",
	"correctAnswer": "D"
},
{	"Question": "How many worms are in the park?",
	"answerA": "4",
	"answerB": "5",
	"answerC": "6",
	"answerD": "7",
	"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{	"Question": "What type of pine tree is this?",
	"answerA": "Kauri",
	"answerB": "Hoop",
	"answerC": "Wollemi",
	"answerD": "Cypress",
	"correctAnswer": "Hoop"
},
{	"Question": "Looking up, inside the spire, what shape do you see?",
	"answerA": "Triangle",
	"answerB": "Pentagon",
	"answerC": "Hexagon",
	"answerD": "Octagon",
	"correctAnswer": "D"
}
]